My dear girl, how I wish I had never
brought you into this wretched world.
Now I see that I've yet
to break free of my past.
Cursed worm, now I'm angry!
No, it can't!
What was it you said about
fate you just climb am i right?
Well i hope you like flying
instead there you go!
Freeze!
Let's go.
Nell 'ingua membo, lachimmo donna Requiem
Nessuno può succedere
un destino scelto Roman
solo il risultato che
non sarebbe distrutto
L 'interna Zoom esiste
solo del me Puoi cantare
canzoni di tristezza
The end of the season.
To be
continued...
It's...
it's her soul!
We gotta act!
No!
Goddammit!
Hey Trish!
Get back here!
Look!
Now to seize my fate!
At last you're mine!
With this victory, fate's
designs are finally realized!
Now behold as Emperor Crimson's
glorious ascension At last begins!
Curses!
Why?
Why does it idle?
Wait, those brats!
What could they have done?
Damn it, I can't grasp it!
No, my...
What foul affliction have you handed me?
How could you children
have broken my grasp?
How?
How can this be?
Whoa.
Whatever had me glued
in there just went away.
What the hell is going on?
This wind, could it be?
What a curious revelation, boss?
Despite all your fervid boasting,
those allegedly flawless
eyes didn't see this coming!
You arrogant swine!
Still, I must thank you—you've
shown us the path to victory.
Requiem's power;
its crux appears to be this luminescent
sphere floating behind each of of
our souls.
One need only crush it.
Your desire for the arrow
stopped you from completely
destroying Requiem.
I, however, feel no such inclination.
It would be very simple.
I could end it all in a single blow.
Wait, Bucciarati.
Think for a moment.
Is anyone worthier?
Can you name even one person? Bucciarati.
You know that I am
worthy of becoming king.
Damn you!
I will never allow your feeble
hands to touch the arrow!
Everyone's souls will
return to their bodies.
Post-haste!
Look, it's rushing back here!
Whoa, that's Trisha's soul! He's done!
Guys, check it out!
Blue Girardi, you did it!
I didn't think you'd
pull it off, but you did!
Now then, Giorno, it's on you.
Bucerati, you're the body that we...
back at the Coliseum.
I don't know if it's...
Giorno, thank you for
all that you've done.
When you and I met for
the first time in Napoli,
when we joined forces against the Family,
though my body became marked for death
by Fate's hand, my soul was reborn.
You revived my faith.
Thank you for showing me true happiness.
I'll be fine.
No need to worry.
Give everyone my regards, won't you?
You imputant wretch!
Such tedious bilge, all for some girl!
You'll rot in hell, you
Philistine mounds of excrement!
I'll be sure to send
all of you there myself!
As soon as I conquer the arrow,
your worthless lives will be mine!
Esu's back.
Way to go, Bucciarati.
Let's never do that again.
Can't have Trish nearly died twice.
Hey, a little help?
I know you're worried about Bucciarati,
but he'll be back here
before you know it, right?
No need to fear, Jean.
I'm simply returning to the
path I was meant to walk.
The path to my origin.
I'm going back.
That's all.
Huh?
Benedict!
Who was it that once said?
We all stand as soldiers,
chosen by destiny.
How quaint this world has
taught me other truths.
Fate has bestowed upon me an extraordinary
power to obliterate
time and see the future.
As such, only one spot suits
me in the natural order.
There is no question.
I, Emperor Crimson, am destiny's
chosen to reign at the top.
A mere soldier I am not!
So why?
Why couldn't I seize the arrow?
It should have been so simple.
How on earth did I fail such a small task?
This is inconceivable.
But it's not defeat.
It may not be now, but
victory will be mine.
For now, I must rest.
I will bide my time and strike
when the moment is right.
I haven't been beaten, only delayed.
My powers will thrust me
back to the top in no time.
Giorno, don't let him run. Stop him.
If he gets away, he'll go into
Hayden, and he'll disappear.
Once he does, we'll lose.
Jean, I can feel him.
He's running with his tail tucked.
Oh, damn!
He's holding it!
Looks like the arrow's
picked its new master!
Nice, Giorno!
Damn it.
It appears retreat was
never an option after all.
I must face him now!
My dignity demands it!
You won't overthrow me!
Try as you might, you will
never tear me from my throne!
I won't run from you.
That would be unbecoming of a king.
Let's end this, now!
When you said he was running,
which way'd you mean?
Is he trying to take us
down with him or something?
Golden Wind!
All right, go Giorno!
Suck up all that arrow's power and show
my father what Golden Wind is made of!
Silly girl.
No such thing will
transpire, dear daughter!
I have to say, I'm glad your
words goaded me into staying.
You've reminded me to
always guard my honor.
Good thing I held my ground.
Had I actually fled, I never would have
gotten to witness this thrilling vision.
Thank you, Emperor Crimson
Eulogy, for this sumptuous sight.
Golden Wind!
All right!
Go, Giorno!
So come on that arrow's power and show
my father what Golden Wind is made of!
But why it looked like it
worked what the hell happened?
How lovely to be back on the
course of victory and right
when I thought despair had
finally Caught me in its grip
but the wounds you inflicted on my
pride steered me toward the right path.
I would not have realized how
truly close I was to winning
without you.
Giorno Giovanna, what did
you hope to accomplish?
The arrow won't sully
itself with the feeble?
Did you already forget what
the detestable turtle said?
My boy, only a worthy wielder
can lay claim to with strength.
How glad it must be then
that I chose to stay.
Time to die like the weakling you are!
Don't just stand there!
Begone, wretched dog!
To be slain by a king!
A final gift!
Just all of us.
No, Giorno.
Wait, Mista.
Look, there's something more than
just blood coming out of him.
I think it worked.
How, how did you?
Impossible.
This must be another trick.
I felt his bones shattered to pieces.
Brain matter should be spilling
from his corpse right now.
So what is this bizarre substance?
Don't tell me.
Did the arrow choose him after all?
Is that what's burrowing into his body?
That's enough! No more!
You die now, Giorno Javada!
Hey, he did it!
Giorno didn't get rejected by the arrow.
It might have taken its time,
but turns out he was worthy.
But it almost looks like the arrow's
become a whole new part of him.
The boss can't take it away.
Call me nuts, but I think
it's stuck to Giorno for good!
What hellish nightmare has engulfed me?
This can't be real.
I didn't make a single mistake.
My hand bore a hole through his
miserable skull moments ago.
He should be on the ground,
dead, in a pool of viscera.
It's Requiem.
Yeah, except this time it's Giorno's.
It's Golden Wind Requiem.
The air around them is intense.
They've transcended the arrow's power.
What?
Perfect!
The only lasting thing is truth itself.
Righteous actions born of truth
will live past the end of time.
My friends are gone,
but I know their virtuous spirits live on.
It was their will that the
arrow be handed down to me.
So let's see, are your
actions founded on truth
or are they the transient
products of shallow evil?
I guess we'll know soon enough.
Are you really as unbreakable as
you repeatedly claim to be, Boss?
What the hell is he going on about?
What's he planning on doing?
Oh crap, please don't
swap our souls again!
Could be that.
Just keep your eyes peeled.
I don't think Jorno's
really certain himself.
But from what I can tell,
we're not gonna have to
worry about him suddenly
losing control over
Requiem anymore at least.
It's nothing like before.
I failed to see it.
His attack managed to evade my prediction.
No, but I did see it
coming, just not in detail.
The vision of a projectile
bursting through my hand,
it saved me from the full brunt.
I can still dodge his
strikes at the last second.
There's no question, Golden Wind's
newfound strength is nothing to scoff at.
But that ends here.
It's gained little more
than a harder swing.
Emperor Crimson can still preempt him.
There's nothing my powers can't overcome.
Enjoy the ride while you can, dear Giorno.
I'm coming to crush your skull
properly this time, as fate ordains.
A little boy like you should learn to
temper his bravado, lest he's punished.
I'll even strip you of any chance
to regret your actions, you brat.
Go, Emperor Crimson!
Time will now be obliterated
for all but me! Excellent!
I can see his stance movements.
His machinations have
been laid utterly bare.
Talentless roaches, at
least try to surprise me.
Amazing how little it takes to totally
neutralize your greatest power.
Poor fools, I almost feel sorry for you.
Never again will you witness the
immaculate brilliance of Emperor Crimson.
The truth of my strength
will be forever lost to you.
At last, I've won.
In the end, I'm still faster.
Your new powers couldn't stop
me from ripping out your heart.
The future can only hold one
of us, and it has chosen me.
Now disappear.
No!
But how?
Damn it, what now?
how is he reversing the
time I obliterated that
shouldn't be possible no
stop it's all reverting
back to normal but still the premonition
clearly shows me emerging
the victor So perish,
Giorno Javada!
What?
What is this?
What the hell is happening to me?
Perhaps this is an illusion.
That curse somehow
pulled one over my head.
Or did he?
The only thing that can move within
periods of warp time should be me!
The answer is plain truth.
Your eyes are not deceiving you.
What you see is very real.
Playing out before you are
the results of your actions.
However, though you might be
able to witness the truth,
you can never hope to reach it.
Your powers are immaterial.
It doesn't matter who you are.
No one could ever overcome this barrier.
Behold, Golden Wind
Requiem's true strength.
Its nature remains a secret even
to my user, Giorno Giovanna.
Lest he's punished!
I'll even strip you of any chance
to regret your actions, you brat!
Wait, that's right before I...
but I...
How dare you!
Only I may bend time!
No, no, my premonitions
always become reality!
The future has already been written!
Emperor Crimson is bound for victory!
Come on, I'll see this alive.
We are the power.
Cause we're the future!
Cause we are the fighters!
Just fighting for a crime.
Let's go, let's go!
Thank you.